Pro Day at The Ohio State University at
the Woody Hayes Athletic Center. [music]
No less than four Buckeyes
slated to go in the top 10 of the NFL
draft. We saw Carnell Tate have a smooth
day today in his route running and
that's something he really wanted to
show to NFL scouts.
>> Really just showcase my route running
ability. That's what I do best.
I'm fluid in and out of my routes and
I'm a smooth route runner. So, that's
what I came to do is play football,
[music] put the football on the field.
I offer everything, the contested catch,
the route running ability, the ability
to get open [music] and create
separation, and also the blocking.
I'm a willing blocker and physical and I
got the best uh mentality.
Every time I see Coach Wilson, we laugh,
we joke, we have fun and stuff like
that. He tell me he can't He love to
coach me if the opportunity [music]
comes.
If all the cards fall right, I'll I'll
be a Saint. Safety Caleb Downs also
worked out. High-pointed [music]
the ball deep and he really showed the
ability to swivel his hips. Uh I thought
I did it really smooth, did the drills
really well, caught the ball well.
Uh showed a little range.
At the end of the day, it's about
affecting the game. Whoever affects the
game, that's who needs to be picked the
highest and I feel like I do it at at
the highest level. So. Yeah, when you
got guys that are a racer type players
in the defense that can play in the
multiple different roles, that can be in
the middle, be outside, be in the box,
[music] be in any part of the field, uh
those guys are going to be on your your
team, your organization for 15 plus
years. You take them whenever you can
get them and that's, you know, that's
Caleb. Uh we good.
Linebacker edge Arvell Reese, well, he
wanted to show that he's capable of
doing all the things necessary to be an
effective linebacker and edge rusher in
the NFL. Just showed that I'm willing to
do the drills, you know. At combine, I
did linebacker stuff today. I just
wanted to knock out the edge drills.
Just do both, make sure I do both of
them because that was my role last year,
both of them.
I think I offer that versatility, but,
you know, it just depend on the
situation I'm going into. If I go to a
place and need me to focus on both, then
I that's what I'm going to do cuz that's
what I did at Ohio State. If I need to
focus on one and perfect one, that'll be
That'll probably be even better. Sonny
Styles, [music] the linebacker, he
transitioned from safety. He didn't work
out today, but Sonny Styles is a guy who
offers you a ton of versatility.
Any job that I'm asked to do as a
linebacker, I'm fully comfortable with
doing because I've been asked to be a
deep half, be a deep post. I've been
asked to cover a slot receiver. So, I'm
I'm fully comfortable doing all these
other jobs I'm asked to do at the
position. The Saints contingent, [music]
again, had a strong showing here. Each
had some some interactions with the
[music] players. This place has been
producing guys that are really high
level and it's really impressive as you
get to know these players. They're
[music] excellent people,
high character, they're really good
football players, they're really
prepared to go in the NFL. And Ohio
State had [music] a grand Pro Day. I'm
John DeShazer and we will see you soon.